<resources>

    <!-- Enter Passcode Activity Strings -->
    <string name="Login">Submit</string>

    <!-- Home Activity -->
    <string name="button_label_friends">Friends</string>
    <string name="button_label_messages">Messages</string>
    <string name="button_label_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="button_label_user_guide">User Guides</string>
    <string name="button_label_logout">Logout</string>

    <!-- Messages Activity -->
    <string name="activity_title_messages">Messages</string>
    <string name="button_label_compose">Compose</string>

    <!-- New Messages Activity -->
    <string name="hintOnChooseFriendButton">Select a recipient</string>
    <string name="enter_message_here_hint">Message Body</string>
    <string name="sendAsTextButton">Send as Text</string>
    <string name="sendAsImageButton">Send as Image</string>

    <!-- Note: button_label_view_messages: "button_label_view_messages", and "button_import_image_label", and "button_import_text_label" were changed after we sent the latest text file to translators.-->
    <string name="button_label_view_messages">Messages</string>
    <string name="button_label_compose_messages">Compose a Message</string>
    <string name="button_import_text_label">Import Text</string>
    <string name="saveImageButton">Save as Image</string>

    <!-- New Messages Activity Alerts -->
    <string name="alert_text_verified_friends_only">You can only message a verified friend.</string>
    <string name="alert_text_select_friend_to_send_message">Select a friend to send a message to.</string>
    <string name="alert_text_write_a_message_to_send">Write a message to send.</string>

    <!--    Settings Activity-->
    <string name="button_label_passcode">Passcode</string>

    <!--    User Guide Activity-->
    <string name="button_label_importing">Importing</string>

    <!--    Passcode Activity-->
    <string name="switch_label_require_passcode">Require Passcode?</string>
    <string name="initial_passcode_definition">Create a passcode so that a login will be required to use the app. Passcode rules are non-sequential, non-repeating, numbers only. </string>
    <string name="verify_passcode_hint">Verify Passcode</string>
    <string name="enter_passcode_hint">Enter Passcode</string>
    <string name="secondary_passcode_definition">Entering a destruction code at login will delete all sensitive data.</string>
    <string name="enter_secondary_passcode_hint">Enter a destruction code</string>
    <string name="verify_secondary_passcode_hint">Verify your destruction code</string>
    <string name="button_label_save">Save</string>


    <!--    Friends Recycler View Item Row-->
    <string name="friendNameRecyclerView">Name</string>

    <!-- Message View -->
    <string name="unknown_label">Unknown</string>

    <string name="button_label_invite">Invite</string>
    <string name="button_label_invite_again">Invite Again</string>
    <string name="button_label_approve_invitation">Accept</string>
    <string name="button_label_decline_invitation">Decline</string>

    <!-- Verify Friend View -->
    <string name="label_verify_friend_explainer">Contact your friend outside of the app you normally use and make sure that your numbers match.</string>
    <string name="label_verify_friend_number">%1$s\'s Code</string>
    <string name="label_verify_friend_user_number">Your Code</string>
    <string name="button_label_verify_friend_accept">Accept</string>
    <string name="button_label_verify_friend_reject">Reject</string>
    <string name="button_label_verify_friend">Verify</string>

    <!-- Alert Strings -->
    <string name="alert_text_passcode_field_empty">The passcode field is empty.</string>
    <string name="alert_text_verify_passcode_field_empty">Please verify your passcode.</string>
    <string name="alert_text_passcode_entries_do_not_match">Passcode entries do not match.</string>
    <string name="alert_text_secondary_passcode_field_empty">The destruction code field is empty.</string>
    <string name="alert_text_verify_secondary_passcode_empty">Please verify your destruction code.</string>
    <string name="alert_text_secondary_passcode_entries_do_not_match">Destruction code entries do not match.</string>
    <string name="alert_text_passcode_required_for_destruction_code">You cannot create a destruction code until you create a passcode.</string>
    <string name="alert_text_secondary_passcode_and_passcode_may_not_match">You cannot have a destruction code that is the same as your passcode.</string>
    <string name="alert_text_received_invitation">Received an invitation from %1$s. Send them an invitation to start communicating.</string>
    <string name="alert_text_passcode_required_to_proceed">Passcode required to proceed.</string>
    <string name="alert_text_unable_to_decode_message">Something went wrong. We were unable to decode this message.</string>
    <string name="alert_text_unable_to_decrypt_message">We were unable to decrypt this message.</string>
    <string name="alert_text_invitation_accepted">${sender.name} accepted your invitation. You can now communicate securely.</string>
    <string name="alert_text_unable_to_update_friend_status">Something went wrong, we were unable to update your friend status.</string>
    <string name="alert_text_which_friend_sent_this_message">Which friend sent this message?</string>
    <string name="alert_text_which_friend_sent_this_invitation">Which friend sent this invitation?</string>
    <string name="alert_text_friend_already_exists">You already have a friend with this name.</string>
    <string name="alert_text_unable_to_process_request">"Something went wrong. We were unable to process your request."</string>
    <string name="input_hint_name">Name</string>
    <string name="content_description_drag_handle">Drag Handle</string>
    <string name="button_label_import_message">Import Text</string>
    <string name="paste_message_for_import_hint">Paste your text here…</string>
    <string name="button_label_import_image">Import Image</string>

    <!-- Friends User Guide -->
    <string name="friends_user_guide_english">Adding Friends:\n
        \nTap the friends icon on the home page.\n
        \nPress the + icon at the bottom of the friends screen.\n
        \nType the name of the friend you want to add and press save.\n
        \nClick the invite button beside your friend\'s name.\n
        \nA share menu will pop up. You will see your invitation to your friend as a message to send. It will look like random Persian text.\n
        \nShare your invitation via your preferred messaging app here. If you are physically near your friend and their device, try sharing by using the nearby or bluetooth options in the sharing menu.\n
        \nThe friend you are adding must also follow these same steps to send you an invitation back.\n
        \nThere are several ways to accept the invitation you receive from your friend.\n
        \nIf you have the invitation message copied to your clipboard: tap the conversation button on the home screen, then tap the import button in the messages menu screen.\n
        \nPaste the invitation message with a long press and select import text.\n
        \nTo share your invite directly from another app, find the text in your preferred messaging app, select all, and choose share.\n
        \nSelect Nahoft as the app you want to share to.\n
        \nWhen prompted, select the friend that sent the invitation.\n
        \nReturn to the friends screen and select the verify button beside the friend you received the invitation from.\n
        \nContact your friend outside of the app you normally use to confirm the information on the verification screen matches your friend.\n
        \nIf the numbers on the verification screen match, tap accept. If not, tap reject.\n
        \nTo delete a friend swipe the friends name off the screen.\n\n
     </string>

    <string name="friends_user_guide_persian">
        \n افزودن دوستان \n
     \n روی نماد دوستان در صفحه اصلی ضربه بزنید. \n
     \n برای اضافه کردن یک دوست ، نماد + را در پایین صفحه دوستان فشار دهید. \n
     \n نام دوستی را که می خواهید اضافه کنید تایپ کنید و روی ذخیره ضربه بزنید. \n
     \n روی دکمه دعوت در کنار نام دوست خود ضربه بزنید. \n
     \n پیام اشتراک را با دعوت از دوست خود به عنوان پیامی برای ارسال مشاهده خواهید کرد (مانند متن تصادفی به نظر می رسد). \n
     \n می توانید دعوت خود را با دوستی که به آن اضافه می کنید از طریق برنامه پیام رسانی دلخواه خود به اشتراک بگذارید ، یا اگر در نزدیکی او هستید ، با استفاده از گزینه های "نزدیک" یا بلوتوث \n
     \n دوستی که اضافه می کنید نیز باید همین مراحل را برای ارسال دعوتنامه برای شما دنبال کند. \n
     \n روش های مختلفی برای پذیرش دعوت نامه ای که از دوست خود دریافت می کنید وجود دارد \n
     \n اگر پیام دعوت را در کلیپ بورد خود کپی کرده اید: روی دکمه وارد کردن در کنار نام وی یا روی دکمه وارد کردن در صفحه اصلی ضربه بزنید. \n
     \n پیام دعوت را با فشار طولانی بچسبانید و متن واردات را انتخاب کنید. \n
     \n اگر دعوت نامه را از برنامه دیگری به اشتراک می گذارید: Nahoft را به عنوان برنامه ای که می خواهید در آن به اشتراک بگذارید ، انتخاب کنید. \n
     \n وقتی از شما خواسته شد ، دوستی را که دعوت نامه را ارسال کرده است انتخاب کنید. \n
     \n به صفحه دوستان برگردید و دکمه تأیید را در کنار دوستی که دعوت نامه را از آن دریافت کرده اید ، انتخاب کنید. \n
     \n در خارج از برنامه ای که معمولاً برای تأیید شماره های خود در صفحه تأیید صحت استفاده می کنید ، با دوست خود تماس بگیرید. \n
     \n اگر شماره های صفحه تأیید مطابقت دارند ، روی «قبول» ضربه بزنید. در غیر این صورت ، روی رد ضربه بزنید. \n
     \n برای حذف یک دوست ، نام دوستان را به سمت راست یا چپ بکشید. \n
    </string>

    <!-- Messages User Guide -->
    <string name="sending_messages_user_guide_english">Sending Messages:\n
        \nNahoft allows you to send encrypted messages to your friends using the strongest encryption available.
        The encrypted message will be transformed into your choice of either a text or an image in order to hide the fact that it is encrypted.\n
        \nYou can only send messages to \'verified\' friends.\n
        \nTap the conversation icon on the home screen.\n
        \nPress the compose a message icon in the messages menu screen.\n
        \nClick \'Select Recipient\' to choose the friend you would like to send a message to.\n
        \nWrite your message in the window that says \'Message Body\'.\n
        \nTap send as text to encrypt your message and transform it into a different series of characters.\n
        \nPress send as Image to encrypt your message and embed it in the image you select.\n
        \nOnce you have made your selection you will be prompted to share the image or text. Here you can select your preferred messaging app or copy it to your clipboard to paste it directly into your preferred messaging app.\n
        \nIf you do not currently have access to the internet, write you message and then choose \'Save Image\'. This will save the image to your phone so you can send it later once you have re-established internet connectivity.\n
        \nTo delete a message click on the message you want to remove and swipe it off the screen.\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="sending_messages_user_guide_persian">
        \n ارسال پیام ها \n
     \n روی پیامهای صفحه اصلی ضربه بزنید. \n
     \n روی نماد مداد در گوشه پایین صفحه پیام ها ضربه بزنید. \n
     \n برای انتخاب دوستی که می خواهید برای او پیام ارسال کنید ، روی \ "گیرنده را انتخاب کنید \" ضربه بزنید. \n
     \n پیام خود را در پنجره ای بنویسید که \ "پیام را اینجا وارد کنید \" را بنویسید. \n
     \n برای رمزگذاری پیام و ارسال آن به یک سری دیگر از نویسه ها ، روی ارسال به عنوان متن ضربه بزنید. \n
     \n برای رمزگذاری پیام خود روی ارسال به عنوان تصویر ضربه بزنید و آن را در تصویری که انتخاب می کنید جاسازی کنید. \n
     \n هنگامی که انتخاب خود را انجام دادید ، از شما خواسته می شود تصویر یا متن را به اشتراک بگذارید ، در اینجا می توانید برنامه پیام رسانی مورد نظر خود را انتخاب کنید یا آن را در کلیپ بورد خود ذخیره کنید. \n\n
    </string>

    <!-- Passcode User Guide -->
    <string name="passcodes_user_guide_english">
        Setting Pascodes:\n
        \nTap the gear icon on the home screen.\n
        \nNext, press the passcode icon.\n
        \nMove the toggle switch to allow the user to require a passcode.\n
        \nThe first two passcode lines set the passcode to gain entry into the app.\n
        \nThe last two passcode lines set the destruction code.\n
        \nThe destruction code exists to remove all saved data and friends if entered into the initial passcode screen instead of the first set passcode.\n
        \nHit save to keep all changes.\n\n</string>

    <string name="passcodes_user_guide_persian">
     \n روی نماد تنظیمات کلیک کنید. \n
     \n روی نماد رمز عبور کلیک کنید. \n
     \n سوئیچ ضامن را حرکت دهید تا به کاربر اجازه دهید تا رمز عبور داشته باشد. \n
     \n دو خط رمز عبور اول ، کد عبور را تنظیم می کند تا وارد برنامه شود. \n
     \n دو خط رمز عبور ثانویه ، رمز عبور ثانویه را تنظیم می کند تا در صورت ورود به صفحه رمز عبور اولیه ، به جای رمز عبور تنظیم شده اول ، همه داده ها و دوستان ذخیره شده را حذف کند. \n
     \n برای حفظ همه تغییرات ، ذخیره را بزنید. \n\n</string>

    <!-- Importing User Guide -->
    <string name="importing_user_guide_english">
    Importing Messages:\n
        \nTo share a received message directly to the Nahoft app from your preferred messaging app: click on the message, press select all, and share.\n
        \nThis will generate a sharing menu and Nahoft will be amongst the apps you can to share to.\n
        \nThe Nahoft app will pop up a message that states: "Which friend sent this message?"\n
        \nChoose the friend that sent the message.\n
        \nNext, the message will appear.\n
        \nAnother way to import a message is to copy the message or image to your clipboard.\n
        \nTap the conversation icon on the home page.\n
        \nNext, click the import button on the messages menu screen.\n
        \nLong press on the white space that states, \'Paste text here to import\'.\n
        \nTap \'Import Text\', and select the sender when prompted.\n
        \nIf you have received an image, press \'Import Image\', select the image when prompted, and the sender when prompted.\n
        \nIf the message is successfully imported, you will see the original text.\n\n\n
     </string>

    <string name="importing_user_guide_persian">
        \n وارد کردن پیام ها \n
     \n هنگامی که پیام متنی رمزگذاری شده دریافت می کنید می توانید متن را کپی کرده و با فشار دادن طولانی در صفحه واردات جایگذاری کنید. \n
     \n بر روی "وارد کردن متن" ضربه بزنید ، و در صورت درخواست فرستنده را انتخاب کنید. \n
     \n اگر تصویری دریافت کرده اید ، بر روی "وارد کردن تصویر" ضربه بزنید ، تصویر را هنگامی که از روی صفحه نمایش کشیده شده است و فرستنده را از شما درخواست کنید. \n
     \n اگر پیام با موفقیت وارد شود ، متن اصلی را مشاهده خواهید کرد. \n\n
    </string>

    <string name="or_label">- or -</string>

    <!-- Content Descriptions -->

    <string name="content_description_add_friend_button">Add Friend</string>
    <string name="content_description_verify_button">Verify</string>
    <string name="content_description_decline_button">Decline</string>
    <string name="content_description_accept_button">Accept</string>
    <string name="content_description_import_button">Import</string>
    <string name="content_description_invite_button">Invite</string>
    <string name="button_label_import_invitation">Import</string>
    <string name="button_label_delete_passcode">Delete Passcode</string>
    <string name="from">From</string>
    <string name="alert_text_message_too_long">Your message is too long.</string>
    <string name="alert_title_confirm_delete">Confirm Delete</string>
    <string name="alert_text_confirm_delete">Are you sure you want to delete this?</string>
    <string name="button_label_delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="button_label_reset">Reset</string>
    <string name="button_label_english">English</string>
    <string name="button_label_persian">فارسی</string>
    <string name="alert_text_confirm_friend_delete">Are you sure?</string>
    <string name="alert_title_confirm_friend_reset">Reset this friend?</string>
    <string name="alert_text_confirm_friend_reset">Any messages you have received from this friend will be deleted.</string>
    <string name="button_label_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="user_guide_button_description">This button will take you to the user guides.</string>
    <string name="settings_button_description">This button will take you to the settings menu.</string>
    <string name="friends_button_description">This button will take you to the friends menu.</string>
    <string name="read_button_description">This button will take you to the read messages, import text, and import image menu.</string>
    <string name="create_button_description">This button will take you to the create messages menu.</string>


    <!-- Help Dialog Buttons -->

    <string name="dialog_button_home_help_title"> Home Screen Help </string>
    <string name="dialog_button_home_help">
        \nSelect the gear to create passcodes. Both the primary and destruction codes can be managed here. \n
        \nThe logout button will only appear once a passcode is set. \n
        \nSelect the button that looks like a book to see all user guides. \n
        \nSelect the people button to create a list of friends. These screens allow you to invite and verify friends you want to share messages with. \n
        \nSelect the conversation button to begin sending encrypted messages. \n
    </string>

    <string name="dialog_button_messages_menu_help_title"> Sending Messages Help </string>
    <string name="dialog_button_messages_menu_help">
        \nNahoft allows you to send encrypted messages to your friends using the strongest encryption available.\n
        \nThe encrypted message will be transformed into your choice of either a text message or an image in order to hide the fact that it is encrypted.\n
        \nYou can only send messages to \'verified\' friends.\n
        \nTap messages on the home screen.\n
        \nPress the compose a message icon in the messages screen.\n
        \nClick on \'Select Recipient\' to choose the friend you would like to send a message to.\n
        \nWrite your message in the window that says \'Message Body\'.\n
        \nTap on \'Send as Text\' to encrypt your message and transform it into a different series of characters.\n
        \nPress \'Send as Image\' to encrypt your message and embed it in the image you select.\n
        \nOnce you have made your selection, you will be prompted to share the image or text. Here you can select your preferred messaging app, or copy it to your clipboard.\n
        \nIf you do not currently have access to the internet, write you message and then choose \'Save Image\'. This will save the image to your phone so you can send it later once you have re-established internet connectivity.\n
        \nTo delete a message click on the message you want to remove and swipe it off the screen.\n\ </string>

    <string name="ok_button">OK</string>

    <!-- New Content Descriptions -->
    <string name="help_button_content_description"> Help Buttons </string>
    <string name="alert_text_invalid_passcode">This passcode is invalid.</string>
    <string name="alert_text_passcode_is_sequential">Sequential passcodes are not allowed.</string>
    <string name="alert_text_passcode_is_a_repeated_digit">The passcode cannot be a repeated digit.</string>
    <string name="alert_text_incorrect_passcode_length">The passcode must be 6 digits long.</string>
    <string name="alert_text_image_saved">This image has been saved to your phone.</string>

    <!-- Enter Passcode Activity -->
    <string name="alert_text_zero_to_five_login_attempts">The passcode entered is incorrect. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="alert_text_sixth_login_attempt">The passcode entered is incorrect. You can try logging in again in 60 seconds.</string>
    <string name="alert_text_seventh_login_attempt">The passcode entered is incorrect. You can try logging in again in 5 minutes.</string>
    <string name="alert_text_eighth_login_attempt">The passcode entered is incorrect. You can try logging in again in 15 minutes.</string>
    <string name="alert_text_ninth_login_attempt">The passcode entered is incorrect. This account has been deleted.</string>
    <string name="alert_text_minutes_to_wait_until_user_can_attempt_to_login_again">Please wait, %1$d minutes %2$d seconds before attempting to login again</string>

    <!-- SaveUtil.kt file -->
    <string name="saved_images">Saved Images</string>

    <!-- Enter Passcode Activity XML -->
    <string name="enter_passcode">Enter Your Passcode</string>

    <!-- Home Activity -->
    <string name="button_label_friend">Friends</string>
    <string name="button_label_help">Help</string>
    <string name="button_label_read">Read</string>
    <string name="button_label_create">Create</string>

    <!-- Import Image Activity -->
    <string name="import_image_hint">Import an image from your device.</string>

    <!-- Import Text Activity -->
    <string name="import_text_label">Import Text</string>

    <!-- Settings Activity -->
    <string name="settings_activity_label">Settings</string>
    <string name="passcode">Passcode</string>
    <string name="destructionCode">Destruction Code</string>
    <string name="passcodeTwice">Re-enter Your Passcode</string>

    <!--Create Activity -->
    <string name="to">To</string>
    <string name="sendAsTextButtonLabel">Send as Text</string>
    <string name="saveImageButtonLabel">Save as Image</string>

    <!-- Create Activity - will delete later - test -->
    <string-array name="friends_spinner_array">
        <item>Jane</item>
        <item>Jim</item>
        <item>Joan</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Friends Info One -->
    <string name="friends_info_activity_heading">Info</string>
    <string name="edit_friend_button">Edit Friend Button</string>
    <string name="edit_button">Edit</string>
    <string name="send_message">Send Message</string>
    <string name="import_text">Import Text</string>

    <!-- Friends Info Two -->
    <string name="invite_again_button">Invite Again</string>
    <string name="verify_button">Verify</string>
    <string name="invite_button">Invite</string>
    <string name="decline_button">Decline</string>
    <string name="import_invitation_button">Import Invitation</string>

    <string name="button_descriptions">
        \nPress Invite to send a key to a new friend.
        \nPress Invite Again if you need to resend a key.
        \nPress Import Invitation to receive a key from your friend.
        \nPress Verify to compare and confirm that your keys match.
        \nPress Decline to reject the last key sent, and start the key exchange process again.</string>

    <string name="delete_friend_button_content_description">Delete Friend Button</string>
    <string name="delete_friend_button">Delete Friend</string>

    <!-- Messages Activity -->
    <string name="messages_activity_heading">Messages</string>

    <!-- Add Friend Alert Dialog -->
    <string name="enter_nickname">Enter Nickname</string>
    <string name="add_button">Add</string>
    <string name="cancel_button">Cancel</string>

    <!-- Activity Friends Info Two -->
    <string name="nickname">Nickname</string>
    <string name="verification_code">Verification Code</string>
    <string name="verified_status">Verified</string>
    <string name="approved_status">Approved</string>
    <string name="requested_status">Requested</string>
    <string name="invited_status">Invited</string>
    <string name="default_status">Default</string>

    <!-- Setting Passcode -->
    <string name="enter_destruction_code">Enter Your Destruction Code</string>
    <string name="reenter_destruction_code">Re-enter Your Destruction Code</string>

    <!-- Message -->
    <string name="from_with_colon">From:</string>



</resources>